Amanda Seale Show. Thank you, Michael Collier. Please tell us, when is this new special dropping
and where can folks get the new children's book? Oh my God, this thing is amazing. Okay, all right,
all right. So some people have been following me for years, so they still know my little story.
So I was on Venice Beach, that's how I started. So I did nine years of comedy on Venice Beach,
five hours a day, every Saturday and Sunday from 1986 to 95, without fail, okay? And I did like
six figures a year. I would do 40 minutes of comedy and 20 minutes of getting my money. And I
would do that five days, five times a day, every Saturday and Sunday. So I became literally the
king out there of performing. When I was on Venice Beach, every morning I buy 10 meals for the
homeless. Anyway, fast forward 25 years later, we're going back out and we're building me a stage
that looks like a king's crown. It's called the King of Venice Beach. I'm going to stay in that
crown for an hour and a half nonstop. But first, I'm going to go to my spot on Venice, gather a
crowd. And I'm going to say, look, we can't block the boardwalk. But I happen to have a stage right
down the street. So we're going to have an aerial view of like 300 people walking with me to this
stage. It's going to be fantastic. But also, I'm giving away 1,986 bags to homeless people full of
goods that will help their life and help their health. Oh, no one's ever seen anything shot like
this. So when is this happening? Friday, May 17th on Venice Beach, we're building a stage right in
front of the police station. You can't even miss it. It's in the center of the beach.